Is that Satoru?
No...
Who is it?
Morning.
What're you doing up so early?
What, you ask? Isn't that obvious?
You're going to school early again, aren't you?
Yeah...
Thank you for the food.
Slow down. What's the rush?
Can I just come straight
out and ask you something?
Go ahead.
What're you doing this early, and with whom?
That's a secret.
It's not something bad, I hope.
Nope.
All right, then.
I'm off.
Hold up.
Take this.
You'll get hungry before lunch
since you're leaving this early.
Got it. Thanks, Ma.
Morning, Hinazuki.
Morning, Satoru.
Here, breakfast.
Isn't that yours?
I'm good. I already ate.
Whoa.
Sorry, Kayo. You must be bored here.
If only there was a TV here or something...
It's all right. Hiromi brought
me lots of books yesterday.
I'm sure it'll be all over in
a day or two, so hang in there.
'Kay.
That was great.
I'll see you after school, then.
Crap! The Izumi Elementary
kids are coming in droves!
I guess I spent too long there.
I don't wanna give the farewell
speech at the graduation ceremony.
What? Really?
Why me? You're better at public speaking, Aya.
Don't worry. I know you can do it, Saki.
Muster up the courage and give it a shot.
Kayo's absent again, huh?
Have you heard anything, Fujinuma?
Nah. I dropped by her place
this morning, but nobody answered.
What happened to Hinazuki?
Think she caught a cold?
Dunno, but it's weird that the school hasn't been informed.
What's wrong?
Normally her mom would have called.
Hinazuki sure is away a lot.
I wanna skip school too.
Well, knowing Kayo, she'll probably
show up all of a sudden eventually.
Shall we begin class?
Okay.
Oh, so you stopped by her place again today?
You must be worried.
Yeah.
And yet you seem to be rather calm.
Like you always say:
At times like these, you need to
keep calm and carry on as usual.
That's true.
Anyway, I called Kayo's house
yesterday and today, but nobody answered.
I even called her mother's workplace,
but they said she hadn't come in.
Sensei! Could you call the
police or the Child Welfare Center?
The police?
Well, wouldn't it cause a certain
someone trouble if I called them now?
What?
I contacted Child Welfare yesterday.
They said they were going today.
I'm going to visit Kayo's place with them too.
If we want to eliminate the root cause,
we'll probably have to start there.
And I can't turn back after giving you the
"Whatever you do, always give it your all" spiel.
Thanks, Sensei!
So Yashiro had already acted to help her!
Yes!
Hinazuki-san? We're from Ishikari City Hall.
No answer, huh?
The lights are on, so somebody must be home.
Let's go around back and check.
Hinazuki-san, are you home?
Kayo?
Excuse me.
S-Sensei!
Don't worry. I'll take full responsibility.
The girl's apparently been
missing for three whole days.
Let's leave this to him.
The lights are on, and so is the heater.
A recent meal for one...
And Kayo's coat is gone.
At the very least,
her mother was here until just now.
She must've escaped out the
veranda the moment we rang the bell.
Damn. We would have at least
liked to take the girl into custody.
Let's come back tomorrow morning.
The mother probably ran out in her nightwear.
She's sure to come back once we leave.
I'm worried about the daughter.
We could ask the police to look for the mother.
No, Kayo's probably fine.
I think I have an idea of where she could be.
If you say so. Let's take a step
back and let the mother settle down.
People from the Child Welfare Center made a visit.
Yashiro-sensei, too.
Your mom wasn't home.
I'm sure things will be settled tonight or tomorrow.
Kayo, you'll be separated from your mother.
Nothing could make me happier.
Child Welfare taking custody of Hinazuki Kayo
would also mean we wouldn't see her again.
I'll be fine.
Thinking about you guys will
give me warmth and strength.
Satoru. It's a bit late, but...
here's your birthday present.
Here.
I'll give you your present tomorrow.
That's a promise.
Thank you.
I get the feeling I've been waiting...
for this moment forever.
You're surprisingly emotional, huh, Satoru?
Huh?
Oh yeah, Satoru. Stay with me tonight.
She's got guts!
That's not it.
Nothing really happened,
but someone came in here late last night.
I was really scared.
A security guard on night duty?
Or maybe the school janitor?
Any other possibilities?
Maybe someone came here to hide their dirty mags.
It was an adult.
He kicked that cardboard box.
I think he was mad about something.
Shall we open it?
Hopefully it's just dirty mags.
What is this stuff?
I was the only one who realized
instantly what this stuff was for.
And it finally hit me that
the serial killer's second victim,
Nakanishi Aya, went to Izumi Elementary School.
We were still stuck in the loop of
the serial kidnapping and murder case.
March 2nd...
At some point between 10 p.m. and 11 p.m.,
Hinazuki Kayo disappeared
from the storage shed at home.
The rubber boot footprints found nearby,
matched with boots found at the Shiratori home.
The killer took her to a commercial freezer
and used a spray to speed up her death.
He then returned her body to the shed before sunrise.
This bus is not safe.
It's right in the middle of the loop of this case.
We should leave here at once.
I guess.
While we'd love for someone to find Hina,
this stuff is kinda disturbing.
Yeah. We can't have a pervert finding her.
Satoru, do you have a plan B?
I do.
Okay.
Let's get outta here, then.
It's the killer's footprint. Remember it.
What's that black powder?
Briquettes...
Don't tell me this belongs to the killer, too.
Damn it all!
Satoru, that stuff doesn't matter now.
Oh, right...
Yeah. Losing my head won't do me any good.
All right, that should do it.
Too bad. It was a good hideout.
Not when strangers show up late at night, it isn't.
Yeah.
Right now, I should distance Hinazuki
from the case, even if I have to push my luck.
Child Welfare is making their move, too.
Our actions are definitely changing the future.
This will work for sure.
Satoru...
This is your plan B?
Yep. Simple, right?
Let's dig deep and take another step.
We're being straightforward after all that?
I'm home.
Welcome back.
G-Good evening.
Explain yourself, Satoru.
This is what happened when I didn't give up.
I'm proud of you kids.
I had a feeling you'd say that.
But I had a feeling I'd get yelled at first.
I said that out loud.
Why would I ever yell at you for this?
You did it to help a friend.
I noticed it a little while ago, but this smell...
I figured you'd be home soon,
but I didn't know how many guests
you'd bring, so I went with curry.
So she knew all along.
Don't just stand there.
Come in and join us for dinner.
Thank you.
We'll take you up on that offer.
What were you gonna do with
all this curry if nobody came?
Well, curry is good for days, right?
Um, here.
Thank you. It was delicious.
Well, leave it to me to clean up this mess.
Oh, I don't mean the mess on the dinner table.
We know.
Laters.
Hello? This is Fujinuma Satoru's mother speaking.
Yashiro-sensei, Satoru and
Kayo-chan came back to our place.
Really? That's great!
I thought as much.
Will Kayo really have to be
sent to an orphanage somewhere?
Well...
I've got an idea of sorts
on how to deal with that.
No, we couldn't meet Kayo's mother.
On that note, Fujinuma-san, I have a favor to ask.
Got it.
Tomorrow at seven, then.
Stay the night, Kayo-chan.
'Kay.
Hello. Sorry for calling so late.
I'm Yashiro Gaku,
a teacher at Mikoto Elementary School.
I'd like to speak to you about Kayo-chan.
He's called Wonder Guy. Isn't he cool?
One of you go ahead and take a bath.
You first.
Okay, but...
Wanna take one with me, then?
Want me to wash your hair, Kayo-chan?
I can do it myself.
Come on.
Are you feeling itchy anywhere, ma'am?
Here? Or maybe...
Here? Or here?
You're 29 years old! Get a hold of yourself!
You'll catch a cold if you don't dry your hair.
Y-You seemed to be having fun in there.
Yeah, it was really warm.
That so?
Wait, those pajamas...
Oh, I bought them beforehand.
She's a demon.
Use this bed sheet. It's been washed.
Okay.
Satoru, you're too sloppy. Pull that end more.
Feels like we're on a field trip.
Speaking of which, the view from
Mount Hakodate at night is something else, isn't it?
You've never even been to Hakodate!
C-Crap!
I-I saw it in a photo...
All right, lights out!
Okay.
What is it?
We don't use a nightlight at home.
Oh, should I turn it off, then?
Nah, it's all right.
Let's leave it on.
Okay, then.
Thank you.
Night.
Good night.
Am I being a third wheel here?
Yeah.
O-Of course not!
Who actually says "yeah"?!
I said that out loud.
What was that for?!
Shut it!
Sheesh...
Stop it!
Are you stupid?
Morning.
Morning!
Satoru, Kayo-chan! Eat up while it's still hot!
Okay...
Let's eat.
Wait, what about the curry?
Saving it as your dinner for the foreseeable future.
There was enough for a half-dozen people!
You could just invite your friends over again.
To hell...
Mom...
Kayo!
Where the hell were you these past few days?!
You little...
You two!